so let's go over how you can use
所以让我们来看看你是如何使用
inkscape to delete part of an image on
Inkscape要删除其上的部分图像
my screen here I have this example image
我的屏幕在这里我有这个示例图像
opened up and for this demonstration I
开放了，在这次演示中我
will be removing the zebra from this
会把斑马从这里移走
image so the result will be an area of
图像，因此结果将是
transparency where the zebra currently
斑马当前所在位置的透明度
is in order to accomplish this I'm going
是为了完成这件事我要去
to be creating a vector path in the
中创建向量路径
shape of my subject that I'd like to
我想要的主题的形状
delete and then I'll be creating an
删除，然后我将创建一个
inverse clipping path out of it so let's
反向裁剪路径，所以让我们
go over how you can do this so in order
按顺序复习一下如何才能做到这一点
to create a shape over my subject here
在我的主题上创建一个形状
I'm going to custom draw a shape using
我将使用以下工具自定义绘制形状
the pen tool let me zoom in I'm going to
钢笔工具可以让我放大，我要
hold Ctrl and roll up the mouse wheel a
按住Ctrl键并将鼠标滚轮向上滚动为
couple of times to zoom in I'm going to
为了放大几次，我要
grab the bezier pen which is located
抓起定位的贝塞尔钢笔
over here or you could press the letter
在这里，或者你可以按下字母
B on your keyboard
B在你的键盘上
and the setting that I'm going to use
以及我将使用的设置
for this particular subject here is this
对于这个特定的主题，这里是这样的
setting up here that says create B
在这里设置，上面写着Create B
spline
样条线
and once that's done I'm just going to
一旦做完了，我就会
zoom in over here and I'm going to move
拉近这里，我要移动
the page around by pressing down the
通过向下按下
mouse wheel and moving the mouse and I'm
鼠标滚轮和移动鼠标，然后我
going to begin clicking to create points
开始点击以创建点
around my subject here as you can see
如你所见，围绕着我的主题
here now that wasn't very accurate so
在这里，这不是很准确，所以
let me undo that if you want to undo the
如果您要撤消，请让我撤消
points that you create at any point you
您在任何点上创建的点
just have to press Ctrl Z I'm just going
只要按下Ctrl Z键，我就走了
to go and create a outline around my
在我的周围创建一个轮廓
subject using the pen tool like this and
主题使用钢笔工具，就像这样
with this setting with the B spline
使用B样条线进行此设置
setting you'll see it automatically
设置后，您将自动看到它
makes the lines curved but if at any
使线条弯曲，但如果有的话
point you want to make a straight line I
你想画一条直线的点我
mean a sharp corner like you see here
意思是像你在这里看到的那样的尖角
all you have to do is hold shift and
你所要做的就是按住Shift键
click and then it creates a sharp corner
单击，然后它会创建一个锐角
as you can see there so I'm going to go
如你所见，我要走了
through here and I'm going to draw my
穿过这里，我要画出我的
lines like this I'm going to hold shift
像这样的队伍，我要按住轮班
put a point here
在这里提出一点
continue along the inside of my path
继续沿着我的小路走下去
here and I'm just going to go around
在这里，我只是要四处走走
this entire subject and trace an outline
整个主题并勾勒出一个提纲
and once you're finished drawing your
一旦你画完了你的
line you can connect it back to the
您可以将其连接回
starting point like that to close the
像这样的起点来结束
path and now we have our shape going
路，现在我们有了我们的形状
around the subject here now let me fill
围绕这个主题，现在让我来填满
this in with the color just so we can
这个颜色很协调，这样我们就可以
see it I'm going to use the color green
看到了吗，我要用绿色。
here and I'm going to get rid of that
在这里，我要把它处理掉
outline I'm going to hold shift and
提纲我要按住Shift键
click on this little red X down here and
点击下面这个红色的小X
now we have a subject that we can use to
现在我们有了一个主题，可以用来
delete part of our image now the thing
现在删除我们形象的一部分
is if we use this object and create a
如果我们使用这个对象并创建一个
clipping mask what it's going to do is
剪裁面具它要做的是
the opposite it's going to delete
它要删除的相反内容
everything except for the zebra so we
除了斑马以外的所有东西，所以我们
want to create the inverse of that or an
我想要创建与之相反的东西，或者
inverse clipping path now inkscape has
反向剪贴路径现在Inkscape具有
an inverse clipping path sending built
构建了反向裁剪路径发送
in but unfortunately it only works with
但不幸的是，它只在
Vector objects so in order to do this
向量对象，因此为了做到这一点
with the rasterized photo like we have
像我们这样的光栅化照片
here we're going to have to do this
在这里，我们将不得不这样做
manually so let me grab this selection
手动操作，让我拿到这个选项
tool let me click off of the graphic to
工具使我可以在图形上单击以
deselect everything I'm now going to
取消选择我现在要执行的所有操作
create a rectangle in the size of this
创建一个这个大小的矩形
image here I'm going to click on the
图像在这里，我将点击
image and I'm going to go to edit
图像，我要去编辑
copy and then I'm going to grab my
收到，然后我要去拿我的
rectangle tool and I'm going to click
矩形工具，然后我将单击
and drag to create a rectangle like that
然后拖动以创建一个这样的矩形
and I'm going to make this a different
我要让这一切变得不同
color than the color we just used I'll
颜色比我们刚用的颜色好，我会
just go with blue for now and then I'll
现在就穿蓝色的吧，然后我会
go to edit
转到编辑
we're looking for paste size and paste
我们正在寻找浆糊大小和浆糊
size
大小
and now I'm going to grab the selection
现在我要拿到精选
tool and with this rectangle selected
工具，并选中此矩形
I'm going to hold shift and click on the
我要按住Shift键并单击
image so we haven't both selected and
图像，所以我们没有同时选择和
then I'm going to open up the Align and
然后我要打开Align和
distribute menu which is over here on
在这里的分发菜单
the right if you don't have it opened
右手，如果你没有打开它的话
you can press Ctrl shift and a on the
您可以按Ctrl Shift键和a键
keyboard or you can come over to where
键盘或者你可以到哪里来
it says object and select align and
它显示对象，然后选择对齐并
distribute and the menu should open up
分发，菜单应该会打开
over here on the right now with this
现在就在这里，拿着这个
menu open I want to make sure I have
菜单打开了，我想确保我有
last selected Chosen and then I'm going
最后一次选择，然后我要走了
to Center this up on the vertical and
要使其垂直居中并
horizontal axis like that and now I'm
像这样的水平轴，现在我
going to click off of it to deselect
要单击该选项以取消选择
everything I'm going to click on just
我要点击的所有东西
the blue the blue square here and I'm
蓝色的，蓝色的方块，我是
going to lower this beneath the green
我要把这个放在果岭下面
object that we created so I'm going to
对象，所以我要
come up here to this menu
请到这里来看这份菜单
where it says a lower selection One Step
在那里它说的是更低的选择一步
press that and it should lower it
按下这个，它应该会降低它
beneath the object we just drew and now
在我们刚刚画的对象下面，现在
I'm going to hold shift click on the
我将按住Shift键并单击
object so we have them both selected and
对象，因此我们既选择了它们，又选择了
go to object and I'm sorry path and go
转到“反对”和“对不起”路径然后走
to difference and now we have this right
不同，现在我们有了这个权利
here
这里
so now we can do is we can click and
所以现在我们能做的就是点击并
drag over everything
拖拽一切
and go to object
并转到对象
clip
剪辑
set clip
设置剪辑
and just like that we have deleted part
就像这样，我们删除了一部分
of the image
该图像的
by creating a clipping mask now the good
通过创建一个剪贴面具，现在很好
thing about this is that it's
关于这件事，它是
non-destructive meaning you can undo
非破坏性意味着您可以撤消
this at any point if at any point you
在任何时候，如果你在任何时候
want to put the deleted part of the
希望将删除的部分放入
image back to where it was just select
将图像恢复到刚才选择的位置
the image and go to object clip and go
图像并转到对象剪辑，然后转到
to release clip and there you go now
发布剪辑，现在就可以了
you're back to where you're started with
你回到了你开始的地方
those objects as they are so I think
我认为那些东西就是这样的
that should do it for this lesson that
本课应该就是这样了
is how you can use inkscape to delete
是如何使用Inkscape删除
part of a pixel based rasterized image
基于像素的栅格化图像的一部分
if you found this lesson useful then
如果你觉得这一课很有用，那么
consider checking out my inkscape master
考虑一下我的Inkscape大师
class it's a collection of over 60
班级它是一个超过60个人的集合
videos where I go over all of the tools
我浏览了所有工具的视频
and features in inkscape and I explain
和Inkscape中的功能，我解释
what they are and demonstrate how they
它们是什么并演示它们如何
work kind of like how I did in this
就像我在这件事上做的那样
video we even have a private Community
视频我们甚至有一个私人社区
where you can ask questions and get help
您可以在那里提出问题并获得帮助
from me anytime you want and best of all
随时从我这里收到，最好的是
there's no monthly membership fees you
没有每月会员费
just pay 17 one time and you're in for
只需一次支付17美元，您就能获得
Life I'll have some information about
生活我会有一些信息
that down below if you want to check
如果你想检查的话，请在下面
that out as always thanks for watching
一如既往地感谢收看
[Music]
[音乐]
thank you
谢谢你